Jhal Hello
Hello Friends our channel today in this video we will
discuss which factors will give
you those possibilities on the basis of which we will
spend our money so let's start
if we talk about the update then
here we see a consolidation in the US market
S&P 500 and Nasdaq here
select my channel which is down
from 5035 to 10 record on their mobile if we
talk then in the Indian market for now
with a little celestial for now
health ki Baikunthi is
4000 current account and
features pay can be seen almost flying right now
which is sister so we are on one side
but our butterfly Divya chose us on Monday at 100 point
comment and share
this first of all we will talk about
placement Nifty with a strip celebration
here every single day has been a low
sperm narrator but
due to the support it gets from the bank in the last few hours we are seeing a little
soft Kapil wind here
If we stop with one hand,
you can
see 1300 on the side here. So,
administrator, you can take a short
position
of 10 here. These gases are
criminal options. The trainer knew about them
here.
And on the opportunity above, the call
contract is still being added here, but the
fruit contracts that we see above are
decreasing day by day. We are
voting here in the market if possible. Now
you can zoom in on some numbers
here. If it is
related to 100 feet, then I will go and call it in the list here.
But now this does not happen. If
we click here, it
is above you. And in the canvas here,
we can also see this train.
If we
do more than 300 on Monday morning, after the next 9 hours,
then you can see 4000 here soon.
And in the meantime, it is
important to talk about it with you in the future,
so subscribe here
because here and others  Because of that,
if we talk about the AR option side, then
here on the black platform below, the call contract is
unwinding. So, as we just
told you, there are more submits on this,
so it only means active, people on the wrong side
and bike express. If we
say club sperm and who is there here, then
you can
see the subscribe here right now and
say it is
intraday. Because if we talk about
your what do you mean
by the way, because there is a
good profit to be made in it, on
Friday. After all this, if we talk about
our stock watch list, then the
first topic that comes in our list is
Indore. Because on Friday there is a major profit in metal and
IT stocks, so
we can see some more profit here. So, like
Guys Interview and Independent,
if you know about some other stocks here, then you
can fit a position in Hindalco
and that is intraday because
if we zoom out here, you will
see some important different things.
Apps voice, here you can see that a
break has been taken and that too 20%, so
you can expect profit booking of 2000 in this for the media people below 407
status, if you click on forces here, then
our next target will be the
parents
and if it is known that it gives you and 5
more
problems, we can consider such tight
that those who should take limit in other stocks,
second is India Post and sequence LIC
result here, due to
obscene old reason, after LIC, we
also got to see in thickness here, this I saw on
Friday, the
stock is not able to bear the support of 2030
and it goes below it, so
for this
[Music]
subscribe, now we
will turn on the gas and we can do
gas or
[Music]
which is for half an hour, if
you liked the video, then definitely like and share
and along
with subscribing to the channel, you will get notification
from this, motivation to you
people
[Music]
which is our third railway
infrastructure and name for the
last one year and
its  The
extra oil that we have added, so now we can add
this rally's
[music]
parents and
up to 302 lovers of any off side link Vaikunth
you
can add eleventh acid up to 2305
these mothers between my drain, if you like
your juice profile in this then you
can destroy it by making your entry and exit as per your convenience, so
for this you will have to do your own NSS
here, after all this, if we talk about
today's visit breakfast stop, then it will be
IPS Bank because its cute
f22 research has come out quite excellent
and looking at this, due to the
current in the stock here, the chances increase significantly in a media report, so guys,
now if we celebrate this consolidation of this stock, if
we see it
coming above 181 then you have to take a position,
and such tractor opium list
5220 ₹1 note here within a few
minutes, you can expect
that if the minister is above its Q2 results then the
profit last year in public  Almost 50%
is big and in difficult here
after December 2015 in the most close loop we have here
you get a great opportunity to
update a position and intermediate you can make a
great profit in it by buying on Monday which is all
in today's video if you
like the video then definitely like and share it and
if you want to know then you will get it by subscribing
and if you have not subscribed to our telegraph yet then
definitely know
because there
you will get some real market information
because you will not get it anywhere else, it is
provided to you free of cost in
gases if you want to
get updates about our school swimming positional traders then
definitely join our
group and
you will see the details of my try plan below till then
thank you so much and I miss you in the
next hi kia a
[music]